<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">UBI Native</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    
    <string name="frag1_text">Fragment 1</string>
	<string name="frag2_text">Fragment 2</string>

	<string name="add">Add</string>
	<string name="remove">Remove</string>
	<string name="replace">Replace</string>
	<string name="stack">add to Back Stack</string>
	
	<string name="checkbox1_title">CheckBox 1</string>
	<string name="checkbox1_summary">Summary of CheckBox 1</string>
	<string name="edittext1_title">EditText 1</string>
	<string name="edittext1_summary">Summary of EditText 1</string>
	<string name="list1_title">List 1</string>
	<string name="list1_summary">Summary of List 1</string>
	<string-array name="entries">
		<item>one</item>
		<item>two</item>
		<item>three</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array name="entry_values">
		<item>1</item>
		<item>2</item>
		<item>3</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string name="harsh_accel"><![CDATA[ 
	    <h5>Harsh Acceleration</h5>
<h6>Pushing the pedal to the metal is not good for your car or safety!</h6>
<p>Never stomp on the gas pedal when accelerating this can lead to tire spin and possible loss of control.  Accelerating at a smoother rate may get you to your desired speed a little more slowly, but it can save you at the gas pump.</p> 
<p>Smooth acceleration is also much more important in more powerful cars as there is a greater likelihood of wheel-spin.</p>
	      ]]></string>
	      
	<string name="distracted_driving"><![CDATA[ 
	    <h5>Distracted Driving</h5>
<p><b>Driver distraction is a leading cause of traffic crashes,</b> responsible for about 80 percent of all collisions, according to the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. Cell phones are the #1 driver distraction, contributing to thousands of crashes and deaths each year.</p> 
<p>Talking on cell phones distracts our minds from driving.  Distraction does not simply involve where our eyes and hands are while driving.</p>
<p>Cell phone conversations can take our minds off the task of driving.  This is called cognitive distraction, and this is why hands-free and handheld phones have a similar crash risk - hands-free devices are not safer! In fact, a University of Utah study found that drivers using a cell phone had a slower reaction time than drivers with a BAC of .08, the legal limit.</p>
	      ]]></string>
	      
	<string name="speeding"><![CDATA[ 
	    <h5>Speeding</h5>
<p><b>Speeding is involved in about one out of three fatal crashes,</b> according to the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration.</p> 
<p>While injuries and fatalities due to other dangerous behaviors, such as driving while impaired and not wearing seat-belts, have been significantly reduced, <b>speeding is still a challenge.</b></p>
<p>NHTSA defines a crash as speeding-related if the driver was charged with a speeding-related offense or if an officer indicated that racing, driving too fast for conditions, or exceeding the posted speed limit contributed to the crash.</p>
	    <h6>Speeding results in:</h6>
<p>•	Lives Lost - over 13,000 each year.</p>
<p>•	Work zone crashes and fatalities - speed was a factor in 27 percent of fatal crashes in construction and maintenance zones in 2005.</p>
<p>•	Unsafe school zones - compliance with lower speed limits is poor.</p>
<p>•	Economic costs - speeding-related crashes cost society over $40 billion annually, according to NHTSA.  Every minute "gained" by speeding to a destination costs U.S. society over $76,000.</p>
	    
	      ]]></string>
	      
	<string name="harsh_braking"><![CDATA[ 
	    <h5>Harsh Braking / Tailgating</h5>
<p><b>Are you following other drivers to close?</b> Keeping a safe following distance is an easy way to help limit your harsh braking events.</p> 
<p>This is an easy behavior to implement but still the most commonly broken rule of defensive driving.</p>
<p>Even if you follow every other defensive driving technique, you can\'t possibly be a safe driver unless you follow this rule each time you drive. If you keep your distance from other drivers, you will almost always have an escape route, or will be able to take some sort of evasive action with ease.</p> 
<p>At higher speeds this rule become more imperative to your safety.  You can greatly reduce your risk of collision by maintaining a large enough following distance.</p> 
<p>At a <b>MINIMUM,</b> during dry weather conditions, you should have at least 2 seconds of space between you and the vehicle in front of you (3 seconds is better).  Do this by using a fixed object such as a bridge, tree, or even a crack or shadow in the roadway. Once the rear bumper of the vehicle in front of you crosses that object, begin to count... one-thousand one, one-thousand, two, one-thousand three, etc.  If you don\'t make it to 2 by the time your front bumper crosses the same object, you need to increase the following distance.  Of course, being further away than 3 seconds isn\'t only acceptable, it\'s recommended.</p>
	      ]]></string>
</resources>
